<dictionary xmlns="http://marklogic.com/xdmp/spell">
  <metadata>
    <package-name>Spelling Correction Dictionary - Small</package-name>
    <date>August 17. 2004</date>
    <version>1.0</version>
    <authors>
      <author>Mark Logic</author>
    </authors>
    <description>
      This dictionary is based on the SCOWL (Spelling Correction
      Oriented Word List) made available by Kevin Atkinson. Version 5
      dated January 3, 2003 was used. It combines Kevin Atkinson's word
      lists size 10, size 20, size 35. Mark Logic added XML tags to
      the combined word list to conform to the schema used in the
      system.
    </description>
    <copyright>
      This dictionary is provided at no cost by Mark Logic
      Corporation, subject to the enclosed restrictions. Mark Logic
      Corporation disclaims any liability resulting directly or indirectly
      from any access or use, whether proper or improper, of (a) the
      information contained in this document or (b) functionality in Mark
      Logic or other application software that makes use of information
      contained in this document. Any reproduction or modification of all
      or part of the information contained in this document is governed by
      and must be accompanied by the attached license and copyright
      notices.
    </copyright>
    <sources>
      <source>
	<date>January 3, 2003</date>
	<version>5</version>
	<authors>
	  <author>Kevin Atkinson</author>
	</authors>
	<copyright>
	  Copyright 2000-2004 by Kevin Atkinson
	  Permission to use, copy, modify, distribute and sell these word
	  lists, the associated scripts, the output created from the scripts,
	  and its documentation for any purpose is hereby granted without fee,
	  provided that the above copyright notice appears in all copies and
	  that both that copyright notice and this permission notice appear in
	  supporting documentation. Kevin Atkinson makes no representations
	  about the suitability of this array for any purpose. It is provided
	  "as is" without express or implied warranty.
	</copyright>
	<sources>
	  <source>
	    <package-name>12 Dicts</package-name>
	    <author>Alan Beale</author>
	    <copyright>public domain</copyright>
	  </source>
	  <source>
	    <package-name>Moby (TM) Words II (MWords)</package-name>
	    <author>Grady Ward</author>
	    <copyright>public domain</copyright>
	  </source>
	  <source>
	    <package-name>UK English Wordlist with Frequency Classification -
	      frequency class 1-16</package-name>
	    <author>Brian Kelk</author>
	    <copyright>public domain</copyright>
	  </source>
	  <source>
	    <package-name>WordNet Database</package-name>
	    <author>Princeton University</author>
	    <copyright>
	      This software and database is being provided to you, the LICENSEE,
	      by Princeton University under the following license. By obtaining,
	      using and/or copying this software and database, you agree that you
	      have read, understood, and will comply with these terms and
	      conditions.:
	      Permission to use, copy, modify and distribute this software and
	      database and its documentation for any purpose and without fee or
	      royalty is hereby granted, provided that you agree to comply with
	      the following copyright notice and statements, including the
	      disclaimer, and that the same appear on ALL copies of the software,
	      database and documentation, including modifications that you make
	      for internal use or for distribution.
	      WordNet 1.6 Copyright 1997 by Princeton University. All rights
	      reserved.
	      THIS SOFTWARE AND DATABASE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND PRINCETON
	      UNIVERSITY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR
	      IMPLIED. BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, BUT NOT LIMITATION, PRINCETON
	      UNIVERSITY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF MERCHANT-
	      ABILITY OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR THAT THE USE OF THE
	      LICENSED SOFTWARE, DATABASE OR DOCUMENTATION WILL NOT INFRINGE ANY
	      THIRD PARTY PATENTS, COPYRIGHTS, TRADEMARKS OR OTHER RIGHTS.
	      The name of Princeton University or Princeton may not be used in
	      advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of the software
	      and/or database. Title to copyright in this software, database and
	      any associated documentation shall at all times remain with
	      Princeton University and LICENSEE agrees to preserve same.
	    </copyright>
	  </source>
	</sources>
      </source>
    </sources>
  </metadata>
  <word/>
  <word>a</word>
  <word>aardvark</word>
  <word>aardvark's</word>
  <word>aback</word>
  <word>abacus</word>
  <word>abacuses</word>
  <word>abacus's</word>
  <word>abandon</word>
  <word>abandoned</word>
  <word>abandoning</word>
  <word>abandonment</word>
  <word>abandonment's</word>
  <word>abandons</word>
  <word>abate</word>
  <word>abated</word>
  <word>abates</word>
  <word>abating</word>
  <word>abbey</word>
  <word>abbeys</word>
  <word>abbey's</word>
  <word>abbot</word>
  <word>abbots</word>
  <word>abbot's</word>
  <word>abbreviate</word>
  <word>abbreviated</word>
  <word>abbreviates</word>
  <word>abbreviating</word>
  <word>abbreviation</word>
  <word>abbreviations</word>
  <word>abbreviation's</word>
  <word>abdicate</word>
  <word>abdicated</word>
  <word>abdicates</word>
  <word>abdicating</word>
  <word>abdication</word>
  <word>abdications</word>
  <word>abdication's</word>
  <word>abdomen</word>
  <word>abdomens</word>
  <word>abdomen's</word>
  <word>abdominal</word>
  <word>abduct</word>
  <word>abducted</word>
  <word>abducting</word>
  <word>abducts</word>
  <word>aberration</word>
  <word>aberrations</word>
  <word>aberration's</word>
  <word>abet</word>
  <word>abets</word>
  <word>abetted</word>
  <word>abetting</word>
  <word>abhor</word>
  <word>abhorred</word>
  <word>abhorrence</word>
  <word>abhorrence's</word>
  <word>abhorrent</word>
  <word>abhorring</word>
  <word>abhors</word>
  <word>abide</word>
  <word>abides</word>
  <word>abiding</word>
  <word>abilities</word>
  <word>ability</word>
  <word>ability's</word>
  <word>abject</word>
  <word>abjected</word>
  <word>abjecting</word>
  <word>abjects</word>
  <word>ablaze</word>
  <word>able</word>
  <word>abler</word>
  <word>ables</word>
  <word>ablest</word>
  <word>ably</word>
  <word>abnormal</word>
  <word>abnormalities</word>
  <word>abnormality</word>
  <word>abnormality's</word>
  <word>abnormally</word>
  <word>aboard</word>
  <word>abode</word>
  <word>aboded</word>
  <word>abodes</word>
  <word>abode's</word>
  <word>aboding</word>
  <word>abolish</word>
  <word>abolished</word>
  <word>abolishes</word>
  <word>abolishing</word>
  <word>abolition</word>
  <word>abolition's</word>
  <word>abominable</word>
  <word>abomination</word>
  <word>abomination's</word>
  <word>aboriginal</word>
  <word>aborigine</word>
  <word>aborigines</word>
  <word>aborigine's</word>
  <word>abort</word>
  <word>aborted</word>
